I had a dream last night that it was the
best episode we've ever done. So, uh, I
couldn't sleep the rest of the night.
Got in here, fired up the old machine
and I'm now waiting on these guys and I
am loose. I got a little bit of a sweat
going. The hammies are pliable,
flexible,
and the jaw muscles are ready to really
ask some tough questions and giggle at
my funny little friends Sha and Will.
Guys, welcome to Smartless.
>> Smartless.
Smart
less.
glass.
>> Hi guys. Shut up, Sean.
>> Oh my god. God, I've never I haven't
last laughed so hard as I did today when
we were standing on the street.
>> We just come out of a
>> a meeting, the three of us.
>> Like adults.
>> Like adults. And Sean Seawn starts to
say something and he like he's doing
right now. He he uh undoes a a top of a
bottle of water and he's about to take
his hip and or no he's going to do it
and Jason slaps it out of his hand
>> and lands on the ground
>> and it lands on the ground.
>> Just a fun little hair fall.
>> Yeah, just a little little fun fun.
>> Just a plastic bottle. Nothing broke.
>> Plastic bottle. So I reach down to grab
it because it falls at my feet and I
hand it to Shawn and as he reaches for
it, I just drop it right before he can
grab it like a
>> That's twice. That's twice denied water.
>> And as it lands on the ground, Sean
reaches down to get it and Jason kicks
it
and it goes flying, hits a curb and goes
under a parked like construction truck.
>> It explodes. Top comes flying off. The
water's everywhere.
>> [ __ ] funny. I was
>> And I haven't laughed that hard. I fell
to my
>> because it was it was high school all
over again. It was like uh it was a
little bullying
>> or just you know
>> it was fun and God clean fun you know.
>> Um Jay, did you like my cheesecake last
night?
>> Yeah. Cheese. Now I I would have I would
have liked it a little firmer. Sean a
little
>> Yeah, it was a little too fluff.
>> You know, it was a little uh it wasn't
as gooey as the last one. So I feel like
we're we're making progress.
>> I like the last one. Now, I say this as
a person who I can't even boil water.
So, the fact you cook anything is
incredible. It's very impressive.
>> But also, I didn't know well either that
I didn't I've never made whipped cream
in my life. I didn't know that you just
pour half and half or whatever in a bowl
and you just start the special whipped
cream.
>> You just start whipping it. I was my
mind was blown.
>> I was like, "Oh,
>> do you think it's a good idea that
you've now learned how easy it is to
make whipped cream?"
>> I think so. I think so. I think you know
what I'm doing tonight. Yeah, you missed
out on a good cheesecake last night,
Will. But then I found out then Sean
told me that the secret ingredient that
he to drive an hour and a half for.
Yeah.
>> Uh was a a a British uh chocolate uh
Cadbury white chocolate bar.
>> No, not Cadbury. It was another brand,
but yeah,
>> another brand that we're not going to
mention. I guess
>> we can if you want. It's called Milky
Bar.
>> Well, we already mentioned Cadbury, so
we're kind of committed.
>> But there's a there's a Is that is that
a thing? Is that normal that there's a
white chocolate candy bar in most
cheesecakes?
>> Well, no. No. I just melted it to make
kind of like the creamy part of part
part. It was one of many ingredients,
but sorry, you thought you tuned into
Smart List. It's uh it's cookless this
week.
>> Bakeless.
>> Yeah. Um Yeah. I I And I I was so
obsessed with getting the ingredients
right. I I drove an hour and a half to
get it because they don't sell them in
the United States.
>> And what did he do, Will, when he got
there?
>> So, you drove to another country? when
he drove an hour and a half away to get
this to what did he do while he was
there? He's like, "Huh? Well, look,
here's a here's a a rare um uh hamburger
joint that we don't have near us."
>> Yeah. Portillos.
>> Oh, that's why you
>> to Portillos.
>> Yeah. And he put a big burger in his
face and and a shake too. I'll bet.
>> Yeah. I got a shake. A piece of cake.
And I got fries and a hot dog.
>> Shake and a shake for lunch.
>> Piece of cake, fries, and a hot dog.
>> And then two beef sandwiches.
>> And what's that?
>> Two beef sandwiches. to be. And this is
when you were on the mission to
>> Were you driving a school bus?
>> White chocolate.
>> Yeah. Well, I had I picked up the white
chocolate.
>> Were you buying for all the kids in the
school bus?
>> No. I never get it. So, we I bought like
a little extra stuff and I put I put in
the fridge. I'll heat it up later.
>> Good for you.
>> Thank you, guys.
>> God. Yeah.
>> Let's get started.
>> Oh, wow. I thought we had But
>> this is really exciting, guys. Today.
You're going to freak out.
>> Oh, it's your guest.
>> It's my guest today. I'm so excited. We
got my favorite red-headed firecracker
here today. She's a self-proclaimed
computer nerd. And before becoming one
of my all-time favorite full-fledged
movie stars, she made people websites
for free. In fact, at 14 years old, she
performed a PowerPoint presentation
titled Project Hollywood in order to
convince her parents to let her drop out
of high school and move to LA from
Arizona to pursue her dreams of becoming
an actress. Thankfully, that dream came
true so we could talk to her today. Her
name is Emma Stone.
>> Emma Stone.
AND EMMA'S A LITTLE UNDER the weather.
>> I'm a little under the weather.
>> That's
>> I can't believe you showed up for us.
>> Did you get into a big pile of bad coke
last night, Emma?
>> Listen, you know what? You've been
there, right? Right.
>> There's meetings for you. Yeah. Listen,
we're saving a seat for you.
>> I know. Thank you.
>> Are you at home or in a hotel?
>> We're in a hotel rehab.
>> It's a
live first ever.
>> Thanks for having me. What an opening.
Emma's been up for 4 days. Listener.
>> Emma, I don't think of you as a ginger,
I guess, per se, when I think of Ginger.
>> But you are.
>> I'm blonde right now.
>> No, no, no. I'm not. I'm actually I'm
blond. I have blonde hair right now. And
I'm And I'm born blonde.
>> Well, I was born hairless, but but then
I grew blonde hair.
>> Okay.
>> Hairless is my podcast.
>> Sure. Give us the full run.
>> Bravo.
>> The uh Yeah, I dyed it red. Yeah, you
were red for a while there. Yes.
>> For a long time.
>> So much so that people thought it was it
was that you were Natch red.
>> Red Natch.
>> But I but I'm not Red Natch.
>> But wasn't it true?
>> My mother's red Natch.
>> Yeah.
>> You got to be careful with that.
>> I have a son I have a son who's a Natch
ginge.
>> Oh yeah,
>> we love a Natch ginge.
>> Oh my gosh. Do we ever love a Natch
ginge?
>> This has gotten so filthy from the very
beginning.
>> I know. Wait, am I fat Nachy Ginge?
>> Hey, man.
>> Do you need a second?
>> Take a nap.
>> I've been up for days. Um, so excited
you're on the show with us, Emma.
>> Thanks for having
>> But wait, didn't you diet originally
like when you moved here and you felt
like you weren't getting parched or
something? I feel like I read something
and then you thought maybe your talent
which your you know seeping talent that
that was
>> that's what I was telling everyone.
>> Yes.
>> And that's what I kept saying and they
went no no no that hair has got to go.
>> But that but that you thought you had to
dye your hair. Is that true?
>> I Yeah. I I was because I I moved to LA
when I was 15. And so all of the all of
the things that I was auditioning for at
that time were kind of, you know, like
roles for 15year-old girls at that time
were a lot of girls that were very I
guess what I was up for was a lot of
very blonde cheerleadery kind of roles
and I didn't fit those very well. And so
I thought if I dyed my hair brown it
would really set me up.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. How'd that go?
You know, it went great. Jason
got parts.
>> I didn't I didn't get any parts after
that either, but a couple years later, I
I auditioned for um for Superb Bad. And
um and I was at the the camera test for
that and uh Jud Appattow said, "Well,
maybe she could have red hair because
the other girl in the movie, who's my
best friend now, Martha McIac,
>> had brown hair." And so we dyed my hair
red and and the rest was, you know,
>> but was did is Sean's incredible
research accurate? Were you really doing
websites for people?
>> Like are you a computer person?
>> I was in that uh kind of, you know, '
90s computer format. I don't know if you
guys know, you know, Angel Fire, Geo
Cities, that kind of world where you did
very primitive HTML. This is not coding
by any mean. I would not if you in fact
I don't have a computer now. They lent
me this computer to be able to do this
with you guys. Oh, do not do
>> I'm like a neolled now, but back then I
was very into the internet and learning
about, you know, building drop- down
menus and things like that. I mean,
primitive like 1998.
>> What What are you looking for when
you're out there? You're looking What
are you looking for in a drop- down
menu?
>> No. See, that's the thing. See, that's
the thing. When you want somebody to
step and
>> this keeps me up at night.
>> If you want somebody if somebody's
looking to step into a really elite drop
down menu.
>> Yeah. If you're if you're looking for
great drop down, if you're in the market
>> now, okay, it needs to be clear. Clear
font. We're not using any comic sands on
my drop down.
>> Okay. We're hitting Helvetica hard.
>> You now are completely um uh You don't
have a computer at all?
>> I don't have a computer at all anymore.
>> Come on.
>> Wow.
>> I really don't.
>> What about what about an iPhone? I have
an iPhone, but it's a very
>> The incredible new iPhone 15. Um,
>> she's Sean.
Yeah, if you want to get rid of your old
one, you know, we're done with that.
Cycle's over. Thank God.
>> We enjoyed our experience, but Oh, mama,
was there a heavy rotation on
>> Sorry about that, America.
>> Um, wait, so you do But you do do you do
email off your phone then?
>> I do email on my phone and I and I uh,
you know, just just type it with my
thumbs.
>> So, no social media, no nothing else.
No,
>> I love that.
>> Come on.
>> No,
>> it's refreshing.
>> Thanks so much.
>> I was thinking yesterday I I I said to a
friend of ours, I says to him, I says,
>> you says friend,
>> I says, "Friend," I says.
>> Yep.
>> I said, "We should imagine imagine the
reset this planet would get if we had no
social media for 6 months."
>> Mhm.
>> Globally.
>> Yeah. Yeah. It' be pretty wild.
>> [ __ ] reset would be incredible.
>> What do you think would happen? Well,
people would learn how to manage
boredom, which I think is a lost talent.
I know. I try to teach my kids like it's
okay if you're bored. That's actually
another word for relaxation. Like, enjoy
it. Take a breath. Being bored is okay.
Like not having anything to do at a red
light or in an elevator is a good time
to kind of like reintroduce yourself to
yourself for a minute, you know?
>> Well, yeah. Do you ever do that thing,
Emma, like where you look at pe I've
been doing it a lot lately. Well, I
don't know where I look around and I go,
everybody's on their phone. Every moment
if there's a if there's a down moment
and sometimes it's reflexive because
people are nervous or you know feel
insecure.
>> Yeah.
>> But when you you wake up in the morning,
you don't have like a loop that you have
to or that you like to do on a computer.
This is good.
>> Well, no, but you computer loop. Well,
you know, you hit the you hit the New
York Times and your email and your
calendar and you kind of get your [ __ ]
>> I just do all that on my phone.
>> Okay.
>> So, I'm probably actually on my phone
more than people that have a computer.
>> But see, what I'm picturing here is that
you've got no no reason or excuse to get
up out of the out of the pillows.
>> Correct.
>> You're still in the feathers. You reach
over, you grab your
>> I'm just in a pile of feathers.
>> You sleep in a pile of feathers for
real.
>> What an angel. What a little angel.
>> I'm down there. What? Like with you had
a nice desktop, you could get out and
into the living room and join the world.
>> Get yourself a desktop. Get out.
>> This is a great This is a great
opportunity for a new segment I'm
calling
JB. Walk us through it.
>> No, you don't want to follow my morning.
All right. So, Emma, which one of your
rad projects are we going to talk about
today?
>> We're gonna There's so many, but I Okay,
so you answer that first.
>> Oh, I don't know.
>> Which one would you like to talk about?
>> I want to talk about our childhood. I
want to talk about all these good stuff.
I want to talk about it. It was your
birthday last week. Happy birthday.
>> Thank you so much.
>> Yes. I mean, lucky.
>> Are we allowed to guess the age? Can we
guess the age?
>> Oh, this might be mean, but sure. Go
ahead.
>> No, no, no. How about I'm going to go
with 24?
>> 25.
Will
>> I'm going to get real.
>> Yeah, be real. I'm not going to put Will
and I worked together when I was I think
19.
>> Yes, that's true. Really?
>> That was a long time ago.
>> You're going to win then. So, wait then.
Wait, then Sean, you go next.
>> Okay.
>> I was going to say late 20s.
>> That's very cute, Sean. And sweet.
>> True. I really don't know. Are you truly
north of 30?
>> I'm north of 30.
>> Oh, she she is uh she is 37.
>> Come on.
>> 35. You're the closest by far.
>> Really? Give a great name. So young.
>> You don't look 37. That I was just
guessing based on what the information
is.
>> Okay. Well, sure. Well, okay.
>> No, no, no. That's true. We did we did
uh we did uh work that was a long time
ago. What was it? What was the job? Do
you remember?
>> It was called
>> The Rocker.
>> Rocker. You didn't
>> Wait, The Rocker. I still need to see.
And what was the other one I said I need
to see the other day? Um, uh, Hot Rod.
>> All right. Well, let's not go through
mine. Emma, go tell everybody who is in
the Rock. Nobody's seen it. Who is in
The Rocker? The cast is pretty
hilarious.
>> It was Rain Wilson.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh, Jason Sedakis.
>> Yep.
>> You. Bradley Cooper.
>> Fred Armison.
>> Yep.
You I need Who directed this?
>> A guy named Peter Katano who directed
the full Monty.
>> Peter Katano. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Uh John Glazer. John Glazer. The great
John Glazer.
>> Who did Hot Rod?
>> Who directed Hot Rod? Was that That That
wasn't Yoro, was it? Yeah. Gotcha.
>> But uh the cast was pretty uh
>> It was pretty wild. Yeah. We were in
Toronto.
>> We were in Toronto
>> and I feel like you weren't there for
that long. I was there for a couple
months.
>> I was there for a week maybe.
>> And uh
>> And what kind of part were you playing,
Emma?
>> Uh well, I was playing the bass in a
band that was fronted by It was sort of
a school of rock adjacent, would you
say, Will?
>> Yeah. Yeah. I would
>> kind of story.
>> Willie, what were you playing?
>> Oh, I played the uh lead singer of a uh
of a hair band.
>> True story.
>> You guys got to check You got to check
it out. And Bradley was the guitarist
and Fred was the the basist. Y
>> uh but it was uh but it was fun. But
yeah, I mean you have not
>> I'm trying to think you just have not
stopped working and doing awesome stuff
since the moment I became aware of you.
You've just been like consistently just
doing cool thing after cool thing, great
film after great film. It's pretty
remarkable. Not a lot of people rare.
basically saying you haven't done
anything as shitty as The Rocker since
The Rocker is what Will is saying.
>> I've done way worse movies than The
Rocker since The Rocker. Oh my god.
>> Subjective.
>> I think maybe it's great. It
>> is good.
>> Let's not go too deep through the IMDb
or whatever.
>> I want to know I met you once very
briefly. You were so kind years and
years ago. Blah blah blah. You never
remember. I think it was at SNL. But I
was like, "Oh my god, that's Emma
Stone." And then so when I did my
research for the for today, I didn't
know that your name was Emily. I want to
know these guy. I know why it's called
Emma, but I want you to tell these guys
why it's why you changed it to Emma.
>> Yeah.
>> And then I also want to know about your
dog bakery thing that you worked at
because I have a friend who lives in
Arizona who has a company. It's a dog
it's a dog poop company. She picks up
poop. Dog poop for you just call her and
she picks up dog poop. But it was in
Scottsdale.
>> Oh, really? That's where I'm from.
>> I know. That's where I was going.
>> That's amazing. We Well, my name was
>> Have you noticed like there's been less
dog poop around in when you go home? Uh,
you know, now that you mention how
Sean's friends,
>> I mean, it used to be absolutely
everywhere, just piles of it.
>> But her gig, her gig is just she's just
a freelance. She just goes around town
and she's looking for just spare poop
that's unclaimed.
>> That's you call her up if you don't want
to pick up your dog poop. And she It's
called poop patrol. Sherry's poop.
>> Who's compensating her?
>> The city.
>> Her her clients.
>> People who don't want poop in their
lawn, man.
>> Yeah.
>> Wait, I'm I'm confused. Wait, so you
call her just to So you just let your
dogs kind of run free on your own lawn
like all week
>> and then poop patrol comes.
>> Oh, they pick everything up.
>> That's right.
>> Gardener comes over, picks up the poop.
>> Yeah.
>> Like
instead of blowing the the leaves and
stuff, there's
>> poop. Huh.
>> Wow.
>> Wow. I don't know. 30 jokes in there.
>> I didn't know where to Well, that's kind
of why I brought it up. It's such a
funny job.
>> You take a tight five and gather them
and then come back to us. But wait, a
dog bakery? You worked at a dog bakery
when you were a teenager? Okay.
>> I worked at a dog bakery when I when I
moved to LA when I was 15. Uh called
Three Dog Bakery at the Farmers Market.
>> At the Grove.
>> I used to go there. You worked there?
>> Yes. For I mean, not for long. For like
maybe six months.
>> Wow. So, wait. This was pre- Ricky.
>> Yeah. This was years ago. Years and
years ago.
>> This was when I was 15. 20 years ago.
>> Yeah. That's when I had my two other
dogs. I used to go there to shop for
them. Do you think that we ever ran into
each other then?
>> Probably. Probably.
>> Huh?
>> I think that I think word would have
gotten out that Will and Grace's Sean
Hayes was there.
>> I think you're right. I think I would
have told everybody.
>> Guaranteed.
>> You probably My god.
>> Okay, so we I must not have been working
those hours.
>> We'll be right back.
>> All right, back to the show.
>> Tell these guys why you changed your
name from Emily to Emma. Well, it was
originally my my name was taken at
Screen Actors Guild, right?
>> Um when I got my card when I was 16 and
>> so Emily Stone.
>> Wow.
>> And so I originally changed it to Riley
because when you tell a 16-year-old that
they can just change their name,
>> right?
>> You pick a cool name. And so I was like,
I'll be
>> number one. You could have changed it to
Emma Middleame Lee.
>> Emma Lee Stone,
>> right? that you that
>> Oh,
>> I don't know if I could pull off being a
three name.
>> [ __ ] Is there any way you could call
her 20 years ago?
>> Could you call me 20 years ago really
quick?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Real quick. Hold on.
>> Just one second. We'll pause.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> And then we'll just
>> That is That is a real thing though,
right? That is a real thing though. All
people who changed their names because
of SAG because there's already somebody.
>> Yeah.
>> Michael J. Fox, I think, was because
there was already a Michael Fox, right?
One of the great ones is Isn't uh I feel
like Michael Keaton is Michael Douglas.
>> Oh, wow.
>> Oh, really?
>> And he changed his last name to Katon
because Michael Douglas was Michael
Douglas.
>> I just learned I just learned Albert
Brooks's real name is Al Albert
Einstein. I did not know.
>> No.
>> Swear to God. Swear to God.
>> That's unbelievable.
>> His brother was Bob Einstein. You know,
Super Dave Osborne. That was Bob
Einstein. And that's Albert's brother.
Or was
>> But anyway, Emily to Emma. Emily to Emma
because well because you're trying to
get to the Spice Girls rout
to Albert Einstein because that because
that was free.
>> That's true. That one's free now.
>> Not being used anymore.
>> Wait, so you so you went to Emma?
>> I went to Emma because growing up I was
an enorm I mean still to this day I am
but an enormous an enormous Sorry I'm um
I'm slurring from all the I've been up
for days.
>> You need to take a nap.
>> Yeah, I got to take a nap. Um, uh, I was
a huge Spice Girls fan. And there was
Emma, who was Baby Spice.
>> No way.
>> Crazy about her.
>> Yeah. Really?
>> I had the opportunity when I was in, you
know, like second or third grade. I
asked the teacher to call me Emma, but
they didn't. It didn't stick. But then I
had the chance to do it permanently and
here I am.
>> Have you Have you met the the Spice
Girls since?
>> I have.
>> Does she know that?
>> I've met the Spice Girls now. I think I
think she does cuz she gave me a really
special t-shirt that she had signed. It
was like from one Emma to another kind
of thing. It was pretty cool.
>> Did you keep it together or
>> I did not keep it together at all. At
all. But I will say the night before I
met them, we were going to their concert
in England when they when they, you
know, had done they did like a reunion
tour a couple years ago in 2019. And the
night before I went to a um a party at
somebody's house and the magician David
Blaine was there.
>> Okay. and he did a uh
>> just an astounding trick, you know, he
he did this this card trick and then it
was this whole thing and it was an
illusion, an illusion, if you will. And
he and it was like he and he pulled up
his phone and the card was reflected in
a picture on someone's, you know, in the
in the glasses of someone on a boat. And
it was this crazy thing. And I got so
excited. Now, this is a tale as old as
time because I'm about to tell you a
story from yesterday as well.
>> I got so excited that I ran. I was like,
I can't stand it because I'm such a big
fan of magic and I couldn't stand it.
And I ran and I was wearing these these
heeed boots and I slipped on the wood
floor. This is the night before the
Spice Girls concert. Slipped. My arm
went back out behind me and I broke my
[ __ ] shoulder.
>> When was the Blaine?
>> 2019. The summer of 2019. So the next
day I'm supposed to go to the Spice
Girls concert and I was like, "There is
no way on earth I'm missing this." So we
got in England one of these, you know,
things from Boots, the drugstore, this
little sling. And I hadn't even gotten
an X-ray yet. And I went and I was in so
much pain that actually meeting the
Spice Girls under those circumstances
was probably better. So I couldn't do
that in front of them instead.
>> And your excitement was so tempered by
the pain.
>> It was so tempered by the pain that I
was like, "It's amazing to meet you
guys. Oh my god." Like it was so brutal.
It was broken in two places. And then
yesterday
>> I uh I have bone density issues. That's
clear because I broke my toe yesterday.
No.
>> Kicking something.
>> Doing what?
>> On what?
>> Getting out of the shower.
>> Yeah.
>> Well, you Well, you shouldn't be lying
down in the shower. What do you mean
getting out?
>> I know.
>> You accident you accident. You stubbed
it on.
>> I slammed I slammed it into something
and now it's completely black and blue
and like all messed up and so I've been
icing it all day. and you're sick and
you showed up for us today. God bless
you. How did you not cancel?
>> It's a dream. This is incredible. Are
you kidding? I'm sitting on a computer
on with with headphones. This is lovely.
>> Half of one of those excuses would have
made me cancel this thing.
>> God, I was just thinking I would
>> This is I was so excited for this.
>> I would give anything for improved bone
density.
>> Yeah.
>> Sorry, just sidebar.
>> Sidebar.
>> We need to take um what is it? Bonva or
something.
There's some pill to help our bone
density, but I've broken seven bones.
Before I was 30, I broke seven bones.
>> Emma,
>> isn't that crazy?
>> Well, so then you seriously looked into
this. You You seriously do have bone
density?
>> I have there's an endocrinologist was
like, "We got to talk about this." Like,
something's up with you,
>> right?
>> And did he come up with anything? just
that I need to take a lot of vitamin D
and calcium and do apparently
weightbearing exercises like heavy
lifting is what creates more bone
density.
>> Well, you could just drink milk and eat
uh like dumplings from Chinchin like
Sean.
>> He says
>> he has a glass of milk four times a day.
Is that
>> No, I I have a glass of milk with with
dinner every night.
>> No, you don't. I really do. You should.
>> Why not? It's good for you.
>> That's Chris. It's good for you. It's
vitamin C.
>> Will you sit at dinner drinking a glass
of milk? Yeah, I saw I saw it a week
ago. So I just I had to stop.
>> Are you just doing it to be adorable or
you really enjoy it?
>> No, he this is what he does.
>> No, I mean
he lives like he's in the 50s. It's
incredible
>> because because water's too boring and
soda has too much sugar, so I just drink
milk.
>> Well, they you know they have zero sugar
soda now.
>> I'm not into it. So listen, uh, I
wanted, by the way, since we're on
medical,
>> I wish this was just a gallon of milk
that I s
one of, you have one of those cool like
million billion dollar voices, too.
>> Is it true that you, first of all,
didn't know you had asthma until you had
an asthma attack while filming EZA,
which I read. And the other thing is,
did you really have a condition
>> when you were a baby because you cried
too much and it made your voice? Is that
true?
>> Yeah. Because you were collicky that you
that gave you a raspy
>> voice like extremely calicky for five
months.
>> What's calicky?
>> Can you imagine now having a kid? I I
cannot imagine having a colicki baby to
that extent. Five five.
>> What does that mean? Collicki.
>> Collic is apparently a condition where
your stomach is killing you. Like
there's you're in a lot of pain.
>> It's like everything I could talk about
is just my medical.
>> No, I know. It's fascinating.
>> But here's what I think it is. It is it
is the it is the uh intestines or part
of part of the GI tract that is still
developing and uncinking itself and
there is a kink in the hose that is not
it still needs to grow to release itself
and it takes a couple of weeks and the
babies are miserable
>> miserable so it was like if I was awake
I was screaming myself horse every day
and I think it was very very
traumatizing for my parents I see
>> you know you know what's good for bone
density is those um those the
astronauts, you know, that thing that
the the power plate thing that vibrates
that's supposed to be good for bone
density.
>> Oh, thanks.
>> Isn't that kind of a 50s thing, too?
>> Yeah. A little belt around you that
>> I read it once over a glass of milk. I
was trying
>> I want to know. Let's get to the career
stuff because it's really interesting to
me.
>> Okay, great.
>> How old your How old No, hang on. How
old is your baby? Let's just do a quick
How's your baby?
>> Two and a half.
>> A sweet. Boy, girl,
>> girl.
>> Girl.
>> Oh, sweet.
>> I didn't know that. That's so fantastic.
Congratulations.
Thank you so much.
>> Yeah.
>> Thanks.
>> With your husband who you met at SNL. Is
did you meet him in SNL? Dave McCary.
>> Yeah.
>> And is he what what does he do with SNL?
>> He he was a a writer director there for
about five years.
>> Oh, nice.
>> Doing digital shorts.
>> And you met him there?
>> Uh I met him there. Yeah. But we had a
bunch of mutual friends. So yeah.
>> So great. I love that.
>> I feel like I was there that week, too.
Although you've probably hosted a few
times. I I I remember I was I remember
being there once when you were hosting
and I was just like, "Oh, she's
>> Guys, wait. Hold on. I'm going to host
on December 2nd. I get to get my five
timers jacket.
>> I'm so excited. I can't even stand it.
I'm I'm like I'm freaking out.
>> You're so good at it.
>> Uh that's really really cool. Wait, so
Emma, you and Dave married in the
pandemic and was that just because it
was planned that way and you just kept
it or were you like, you know what,
let's just do this now?
>> You were waiting for a pandemic, weren't
you? Didn't you guys say you wanted to
get married, but let's wait for a
pandemic to hit?
>> I read that somewhere.
>> Trim the fat a little bit on the invite
list.
>> Yeah. You know,
>> smart.
>> The week that I got married, I I did
open a refrigerator and the handle broke
off and I got a black eye.
>> Oh my god. Oh my god.
>> And that's where it stops. You know, I
do need a helmet.
>> I need a helmet and extensive. You got
this new show with Nathan Fielder. I
want to skip ahead. I know she's your
guest. Oh yeah.
>> But that that looks really
>> I know she's your guest, but I'll take
this one.
>> But I say it looks really fun. First of
all, he's great. And not just because
he's Canadian. He's super funny.
>> You're super funny. And when I first saw
the ad for it, I was like,
>> "These motherfuckers." And then they got
one of those safties in there.
>> Yeah, they sure did. Put a wig on him.
>> Took a boom out of his hand and said,
"Go."
>> This is like a [ __ ] This is like a
[ __ ] talent explosion happening in
one thing. I'm so goddamn excited for
this thing. I haven't se I'm so excited
for this.
>> It's a wild ride that one.
>> Tell us how did that come to you to your
orbit,
>> Nate? So, Nathan and I have known each
other through through Dave and and uh
Dave's best friend, Kyle Mooney, have
been love. Huge
>> and they've been best friends since they
were 9 years old. So, they're Yeah. And
and so Nathan uh knew Dave and Kyle well
and I got to know Nathan uh for a couple
years and then I think in 2020
2019 maybe uh Nathan called me and said
that he and Benny Safty had come up with
this kind of loose idea for a show based
on something that Nathan had really
experienced where
someone had said that they curse him
>> in a moment And he was like, "This
probably isn't true, but he found that
it haunted him."
>> Sure.
>> And they started coming up with this
sort of premise of what what would
happen if you're kind of going about
your life and they had this idea for
this couple who is trying to create
their own HGTV show. But early on,
>> right,
>> the husband, a little girl says, "I I
curse you." and if that hangs over the
the premise of this whole show
>> and how that evolves and kind of makes
them go crazy. Um whether it's, you
know, real or not. And it just sort of
spiraled out from there and became this
this very uh intense uh show. It's
really it it is a comedy, but it's kind
of not a comedy.
>> Kind of dark. Yeah,
>> it's very uh Yeah, there's a there's a
lot going on there. So, it was No, it
was a blast. And we were we were in um
in New Mexico for like half of last year
um shooting that. And
>> And say the title again.
>> The curse.
>> Yeah, The Curse. I see posters for it
everywhere.
>> And say the title one more time.
>> And what the third time does.
>> Um so, um The Curse.
>> I want to talk about poor I want to talk
about Poor Things, too, which is
>> a movie that you have coming up.
>> The brilliant.
>> I'm going to go see it this week.
>> You are?
>> Yeah.
>> I can't.
>> Where are you going to see it? I'm
seeing it uh
>> at one of the screening because I'm
going I'm gonna be at those.
>> Yeah, I'll see you there.
>> I just got a text for it. Yeah.
>> Oh, great. Was it me texting you to
come?
>> It was you. Where do you do you go by
Emma Stone?
>> Oh.
>> Oh, shoot. It is.
>> Interesting. Yeah.
>> Um this is the second project with
Yorgos. Yes. It was technically the
third because we made a short film um at
the beginning of 2020 and then so but it
was it was yes it was the second so
brilliant.
>> Amazing.
>> We made another one in the meantime. We
made another one in New Orleans last
year.
>> No, really.
>> Yeah. With with uh with
>> Will. Yeah. And William and Poor Things.
>> Yeah. We've done two together. And so
for my for my sister Tracy, um, Yorgos
did the favorite, the lobster, just a
bunch of sacred deer.
>> Incredible.
>> Dog tooth, which is
>> so poor things. So So did you develop
it? Did you find it? Like did you just
get an offer? Like how did that come
together? So, so, uh, Yorgos and I did
The Favorite, uh, in 2017. And right as
we were wrapping up The Favorite, he
told me about this book that he and Tony
Magnamera, who was the writer of The
Favorite,
>> Mhm.
>> had had optioned and they were working
on adapting. And he just told me the
premise of it. And I was like, I I beg
of you. I have to do this with you.
>> Yeah. And so for the next few years, we
uh worked on things and started kind of
putting it all together and um and he
asked me to be a producer on it, which
was amazing. And so we kind of like
assembled this team and then uh at the
end of 2021. Why do I keep saying all
the dates?
>> Yeah. I don't know.
>> Cuz you're like Will. You have
incredible recall on dates.
>> I have I do everything by date.
>> So really
>> month and year. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Me, too. Everybody's birthdays. Do you
forget a birthday? Oh,
>> can you forget a birthday once?
>> I can forget a birthday, but if you say
like, hey, like I can say like, oh yeah,
like it was that time of year, that
year.
>> It was this month,
>> March of 2023. He knows a difference
between April of 21 and March of 24.
>> Maybe I function similarly.
>> Yeah, but anyway. So
>> anyway, so we made it we made it two
years ago and um and yeah, it's just
it's it's uh it's probably my favorite
my favorite thing I've ever gotten to
do.
>> Really? Yeah.
>> Wait, so with you you you work all the
time constantly it seems like which is
great and everybody can't get enough of
you and so when you go from when you go
from set to set
>> other than your child do you have like
something how do you set it up so it's
home or how do you set it up so it feels
like all right I need to have at least
this this and this in my trailer or this
this and this with me?
>> What a fun question.
>> I'll tell you I'll tell you three things
that always keep me company no matter
where I am.
>> Coke
>> app. Sorry.
>> Big plate of Coke.
>> Just she got to get through it.
>> Like obsessed with the idea that I'm on
Coke just because I'm on cold medicine.
Jason,
>> go with it.
>> You know, just suffering through ass on
cold medicine.
>> She's here on
a broken
broken foot.
>> I'm near death.
>> I know. I can't believe it.
>> Um, no. I uh apples and peanut butter.
>> Really?
Really?
>> Every day for a snack I have apples and
peanut butter. Every day I have a
Starbucks coffee. Doesn't matter where I
am. Could be in the greatest coffee
places in the world. Europe, wherever.
Doesn't matter. Find a Starbucks.
>> And what's your choice?
>> A coconut misto.
>> Coconut.
>> What is it? A coconut? What?
>> It's Listen, they make you say misto,
which you know the Starbucks lingo where
they make you say these things. It's a
venty coffee. Just a regular venty
filter coffee. drip coffee,
>> a large
>> with steamed coconut milk.
>> Okay.
>> And that's the that's the misto part.
>> That's the misto. That's what makes it a
misto.
>> So that's not a latte.
>> That's not a latte. No, cuz it's not
espresso.
>> So you have apple. By the way, I have
peanut butter and rice cakes always
>> every day.
>> Well, that's my treat. That's my snack.
>> That's your treat.
>> Yeah, that's my snack if I like in a
minute after.
>> Peanut butter and rice cakes.
>> Oh, I love that.
>> That's a healthy treat. It's not like
you go and get all the Twizzlers from
the Why do you guys go with just the
apple or just the rice cake? Why do you
need to spread all the fatty
>> nut?
>> Peanut butter gives you a little hit of
protein and big hit of joy.
>> I like the peanut butter with the
apples.
>> It's delicious.
>> Sean, explain for not for Tracy, but for
Jason what joy is.
>> It's another kind of peanut butter.
>> Not for
>> Oh, no. That's Jiffy.
>> Um Emma, like when I you were so [ __ ]
phenomenal in The Favorite and you won
for the favorite, right?
>> Yes, she did. No.
>> Yes. nominated. Yes, we did.
>> She was She was fantastic though.
>> Thank you so much.
>> Nominated.
>> Wait, but what was Is that
>> You won a nomination is what I meant.
>> Did you really not win? I can't
remember. You did win.
>> Not for the not for the favorite. No.
>> Well, which one did you win for?
>> La.
>> Oh, that's right. La.
>> Um, so I love that movie, too. Um, God,
you're so
>> That's a truly embarrassing thing to
have to sit here and say.
>> No,
>> not for not for that one.
>> No, I want to know. I asked. I want to
know. everything.
>> Um, but wait, the favorite was you were
super
>> My mom says I'm always a winner.
>> Yeah. And always her favorite. Huh.
>> Exactly. Exactly.
>> But was that cuz when I w when I've seen
that movie, when I watched that movie, I
was like, "Oh my god, this just looks
like a colossal amount of work." That
movie, The Favorite, like it just looks
so grand and so massive.
>> That's just because a lot of it was in
that fisheye lens. That's what makes it
look so grand.
>> All right.
>> You know what I mean? That was a little
trick of the trade.
>> That was in England. Yes,
>> that was in England.
>> And La La Land was here in Los Angeles.
>> In LA. Yes.
>> Favorite favorite such a good movie. I
just wanted to apart from the work that
you know these guys are so tired. But I
I that movie was so good. Emma Stone.
>> We'll be right back.
And now back to the show.
>> Um was that that one of the hardest
things you've ever done? on that. What
was the What's the hardest one you've
ever done?
>> Oh god.
>> Physically, emotionally, both. Whatever.
>> La La Land had a bunch of stuff in it.
>> Oh yeah. You got to learn
>> the the hardest thing I've ever done was
on stage.
>> Yeah.
>> By far.
>> Sean loves stage stories.
>> I do. You know, I do.
>> Well, I've only done one professional
stage show like 10 years ago. Oh, you
want a what went wrong story?
>> I wanted like a bad theater story. But
here's the I did I did Cabaret and I
only did it for for three and a half
months which is so short by by stage
terms
>> but enough
>> I thought I truly going into it I was so
beyond excited. It was it was probably
the greatest experience of my life for
the same reason. And I was like, "Oh,
you just do it at night and then you do
two shows a day on Wednesday and you do
two on Saturday and it's just and then
you're at home and you're just it your
entire life is eaten." The and it is so
hard. You have to live like a monk. Like
there's nothing or at least I did
because I lose my voice and I had to
sing and it was like I've I've never
experienced something that that
physically uh taxing as an actor.
>> Yeah. It was it was unreal.
>> I'm sure
>> that was the hardest.
>> And when you when you But did you did
anything go massively wrong? Do you have
like a any kind of night where you're
just like, "Oh [ __ ] my voice nothing
came out when I sang or somebody
>> Yeah, I mean I had steroids multiple
times like no. Yeah, no heart attacks in
the house. Thank God. But that's there
there are a lot of those stories." But
that No, I I um just to add to my you
know things that are wrong with me,
>> I'm extremely blind. Blind blind as a
bat.
>> Okay. And I wear uh contacts for that.
And uh they both popped out of my eyes
while I was singing maybe this time.
>> And there's And it cuts.
>> Really been reaching for a note.
>> It cuts. I was really Yeah, I'm always
reaching for those notes. That's I'm not
a a singer per se. And the And the
lights went dark and and you have to,
you know, go off in the in the blackout
>> and I couldn't see a thing in the world.
And I just went and like slammed into it
was terri that getting off stage not
being able to see it all was
>> and then couldn't find the contacts
right they were on the floor in the
>> couldn't find it but I no I always bring
spares I have to travel with spares.
>> Yeah it's very
>> great if you did the rest of the play
with glasses on would have been great.
>> You came back out with glasses.
>> Yeah. All of it gives me so much
anxiety. But um when when you
>> I always had a fear Sean of getting
hiccups on stage. Yeah.
>> Oh my god that's a great fear.
>> Have you had hiccups on stage?
>> No. But I had one thing where I had like
allergies and I could feel the
post-nasal drip in the back and it was
right before I had to sing. What do you
get when you fall in love? You know,
with Chris and um I was literally like
what?
>> Oh no.
>> Like forever.
>> Oh god.
>> It was the worst. Panic, tears, cuz I
couldn't cough, but I had to act like I
was everything. It's the I have a
million
>> Okay, I'm about to I'm about to tell you
guys something that I think that you're
not going to enjoy. I know Jason's not
going to enjoy this. Oh no.
>> What do you do when you get I'm gonna
ask you guys. I'm gonna go around to the
panel here. What do you guys do when you
get the hiccups?
>> Do you have like a surefire?
>> I don't have one.
Emma, go first.
>> I have a cure, but people tell me that
I'm wrong. But if not, if you do it
right. Okay,
>> here's the thing.
>> Yeah. You don't scream at people.
>> This is the solve. Put your arm up above
your head. Just take one arm. Put it up
above your head. Well, just because I'm
I'm right-handed, so if you're if you're
left-handed, you could do it.
>> Drivers don't do this.
>> You take your Don't do it if you're
driving. Now take water and you're going
to and I'm talking like tiny sips. You
go swallow, swallow, swallow, swallow as
you lower your arm slowly.
>> Well, nothing's going to happen cuz none
of look at all of us. We're all doing
it.
>> Well, we're just practicing.
>> Listeners, we're all doing it.
>> We're practicing.
>> I'm telling you, it is 100%
do it correctly. Really,
>> I feel amazing.
>> What do you guys do, Sean or J?
>> I I
>> Nothing.
>> I I um
>> I wish I had something. take a deep
breath.
>> Try this.
>> And um and I kind of let it feel it kind
of go away. And then I take water while
I'm holding my breath. It seems to work.
>> I've never told anybody I've never told
anybody this. This is this is absolutely
true and I can't believe I'm telling it.
>> We're ready. Uh, anytime I get the
hiccups, uh, and I remember one time
vividly years ago, our buddy Edgar
Wright would did this thing, um, called
Don't, which was like a, it was like a
fake movie trailer between uh, uh, there
was a double bill, like a Robert
Rodriguez film or whatever, and he made
this fake trailer, and I did the voice
for anyway, I remember going to record
the trailer voice because I do don't
even breathe, don't even blah blah blah.
I did this whole thing, right? I was in
the West Village at this recording place
and doing the thing and I had had a soda
I think and I got the hiccups cuz I was
>> taking in so much air and I was like
what the [ __ ] This is where I learned
it and I was like uh just give me a
second just got to cuz I'm like
hiccoping on, you know, trying to record
and I go into the bathroom uh
>> and I stick my finger down my throat and
I make myself gag and throw up a little
bit.
>> Yeah.
>> Gone.
>> Yeah. Gone.
>> I came back out and I finished. And
that's what I do every time when I get
the hiccups now. I go, "Excuse me, I get
it."
>> That is disgusting.
>> There's a better way, Will.
>> I don't know. It works.
>> Do you Do you fully throw up or do you
gag?
>> E. Well, it depends on where I'm at. You
know what I mean? Depends on what's
going on.
>> Hiccups that much that you'll just make
yourself puke.
>> I hate hiccups. I will be.
>> But this was Were you just gambling that
this would work or was this something
you kind of read about?
>> I was just gambling. I had no idea and I
just did it.
>> Wow. That is
>> Huh.
>> I did not know this. You have a tattoo
on your arm or your wrist or somewhere?
>> My wrist.
>> I want to see
>> very a very very very poorly done
tattoo. Look at this. Now, this was
supposed to be I just want you to
understand
>> this was based off of a drawing that was
drawn with a pencil. Okay.
>> It looks like bird feet.
>> Does that look like a pencil?
>> Is it a cactus?
>> Looks like
>> it's bird feet. And it bleeds out more
and more every single year. I got it 13
years ago and it just keeps spreading. I
in 20 years this is just going to be
>> What kind of halfass tattoo artist?
>> Were you in a French prison or
something?
>> I went into just kind of a random tattoo
place on 14th Street and I was just Yes.
>> Why didn't you consult with Why didn't
you consult with the sleeveless one? He
could have hooked you up with a with a
great tattoo artist.
>> And now I've gone to to good tattoo
artists and said, "Can I get this
lasered off and redone?" And they were
like, "Your skin is so thin there that
it's probably just gonna look like
you're burnt. Like it might be worse."
>> Oh, really? So, wait,
>> I don't know what to do.
>> And your mom got the same one.
>> My mom, my dad, my brother. I mean, the
story behind it is so special. But it
was like And theirs all look
>> great, by the way, cuz they all went to
better tattoo people. And I like I'm the
one who has to cover it up for work
every day. And it's like raised up. It's
really
>> Don't you hang out with thorough just a
little bit?
>> Oh, I know.
>> Yeah. Okay. So, he could have hooked you
up with somebody with maybe a better
>> I didn't know him then.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> This was 2010.
>> I love that your whole family has it
though.
>> Any thoughts on Justin?
>> This was October of 2010. Will, you
remember?
>> I love that. I love that. By the way, I
I wasn't going to say it before, but you
know when we shot the rocker, it was
June of 2007. Okay.
>> I know. I know. I know. You know, I know
you know. I know. You know. Um, uh,
uh, that is, yeah, Jason brought up a
good point. Any thoughts on thorough?
And by the way, this is a safe safe.
>> Anything hurtful that you can think of?
>> Another segment we're introducing.
>> Well, you know, he he suffers from
eczema.
>> There we go.
>> Does he really?
>> That's why he doesn't wear sleeves cuz
he's proud and he wants to show it.
That's right.
>> No, that's not really Is he a Sky Rizzy?
>> I don't know if he really does suffer
from eczema. It's just we, you know,
we've had a lot, we've had skincare
conversations, as I'm sure you,
>> you know, we we once put on his
Wikipedia page that he cries when he
orgasms.
>> Um, it's true. Kimmel,
>> did someone take it off?
>> He did. He did. He
>> He did like an hour later.
>> I guess he got an alert or something.
Yeah, Kimmel knows how to like break
into someone's Wikipedia page. He put
>> the wrong person to know how to do it,
too.
>> Yeah, I love that.
>> Will you guys put something on my
Wikipedia page? Don't put that one. Put
something different.
>> No. Yeah, we'll we'll put Jimmy's brain.
>> We're going to put cries when Justin
throw orgasms.
>> Please. Please don't put that.
>> Oh, it would be funny. See how long it
>> would be funny though.
>> Can I ask about like early early because
you have a brother, right?
>> I have I have a younger brother.
>> Close with your brother.
>> Very. Yeah.
>> Oh, that is he in the business.
>> Just the two of us. No. No. He works in
at like a tech company. And growing up,
did was he interested or no? He was less
like you. You do that. I'm gonna go over
here.
>> Not at all. He played football.
>> Yeah. Where was home? Where did you grow
up?
>> Scott, Arizona.
>> With the poop. With the poop.
>> Remember Remember earlier? That was the
same conversation.
>> Huh?
>> Yeah. How long have you been talking?
>> Remember from before it was like 20.
>> Um, what did you say? What did you say?
>> From earlier.
>> Um, and uh, good thoughts, good feelings
about Arizona. Do you miss it out there?
You still have family out there?
>> I do. Yeah, I still have family out
there. It The thing about
Arizona is it's so hot. It's so
oppressively hot.
>> Yeah.
>> It's It's difficult to You need to be
built for that kind of heat. And I I'm
not
>> It's not a fun heat.
>> It's not a fun heat at all. It's like
120 degrees daily.
>> Yeah.
>> And we're going to end I want to I
wanted to ask you this because we're
going to end on a industry business
question. I love a a biz a biz kid.
>> I love the bizry. I love the bizry.
>> I love I love the heat. I love the buzz.
>> Y
>> um when you you know a lot of people who
win an Oscar like you did for La La
Land, they you were amazing. So
deserved. I loved that movie. I loved
you in it. Did you um A lot of people
who win sometimes it's it's known as the
curse of death with some actors.
First of all, I should ask, are you guys
locked? Or before I give you these,
>> are you picture locked on Laand? Cuz you
got the Oscar. Great.
>> But couple things.
>> Were it me?
>> I tried a little harder.
>> I got some I got some notes.
>> Yeah, for you.
>> I was going to say, how did you Were you
nervous? Did you Did you have anxiety?
You're like, "Oh my god, this is so
great. I won the Oscar." But did you
have did you feel like I don't know. A
lot of the times some actors who win
Oscars, you kind of don't see them for a
long like years and years and years.
Were you Did you have anxiety about like
crap, I won, now people are sick of me?
>> Nope. Sean, nobody felt that. Well, why
would
>> not that I was? No, but just
>> [ __ ] what kind of psycho.
>> First thought is put that out there in
the world. You must hate me now.
>> Okay, Sean, why did you tell us how you
feel?
>> Sean, when you won the Tony, is that
what you were saying when you were
walking up to your kids to get the Tony?
>> Check Sean off my list. I know how
>> Thanks for having me today.
>> That came out wrong. What I what I meant
was like did you have anxiety about like
I'm not going to work. People are like
people think must think like oh we you
made it.
>> I left that I this was a very uh lucky
situation cuz I had I met Yorgos while
we were filming La La Land and I left
the day after the Oscars to go shoot the
favorite.
>> Oh, that's great. So, it was kind of
amazing because the next day I went
right back to work and was back in.
>> Did you have time to renegotiate your
deal on your way to location?
>> Yes. So, that was I did delay my flight
for a couple hours just to call just to
call my lawyer. But,
>> by the way, that was
>> reopened just the salary portion.
>> New deal points that I'd love to
>> No, but by the way, um that was a big
compliment is what I know can come up.
>> Okay. Okay. Okay. How many great because
you've been you've been nominated I'm
sure a million times forward
>> I think it's a it's a million
>> lots of great awards do you have do you
have do you have a bunch of great unused
uh acceptance speeches
>> no what no
>> I'll bet you do
>> I bet you I'll bet no but I bet I bet
you give some thought some respectful
time and some thought to what you would
say up there you're not one of these
ingrates that would just ah if I win I
win I'll just go up there and wing it I
bet you've got some fun stuff that you
said I Just my dream is to have like a
book a coffee table book of people's
unused acceptance speeches.
>> That's a great idea. That's a really
good idea.
>> That's a really good idea,
>> right? Huh?
>> That maybe you should maybe you should
start compiling it.
>> Have to be anonymous though, wouldn't
it?
>> Well,
>> right. The the people with the speech.
>> Yeah, cuz I guess it would be But then
how do you do an anonymous acceptance
speech? Everyone would know who it was.
Like the people they're thanking.
>> What were we gonna say for the rocker?
>> Yeah. If you had gotten up there for the
rocker, who would you thank first?
Probably just Will.
>> Yeah. Oh gosh. Will, thanks for being
our guest today. Thanks for having me.
>> No, but you did you got nominated for
you got nominated for La La Land, which
you won. You got nominated for The
Favorite and you got nominated for
>> Silence.
>> The Birdman. Is it the Birdman?
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> And you had to work with Galanakis.
>> Oh, God. I know.
You wouldn't.
>> Is there least is there is there a less
talented guy in showbiz than Zack
Alfanakis?
>> You know, from from your lips to God's
ears.
>> I know. I agree. I couldn't agree more.
>> He was he was so so sweet that whole
Anyway, yeah. No, he really is.
>> What are you going to do for us tonight?
And are you watching Golden Bachelor?
>> No. What's Golden Bachelor?
>> I love that answer. I love that answer.
>> What is Golden Bachelor? It's the
Bachelor but you should never know what
it is. Emma Stone, this is why you are
you. Cuz you don't know.
>> I'm just out here breaking bones,
getting sick, not watching Golden
Bachelor.
>> Um, well, now I'm going to look it up
and watch.
>> Went through a phase. Sean went for a
phrase where is Breaking Bones, right?
>> Yeah.
>> Early 20s Chicago.
>> Hey. Hey.
>> Oh god.
>> Hey, Emma. Cool it. All right.
>> Okay. Okay. Sorry. Sorry about that.
Sorry.
>> Um, Emma Stone, we're going to let you
go. We're going to let you heal. We're
going to let you get better. We're going
to make you feel better. We're going to
I'm going to send some soup over.
>> You don't need to send anything. It'll
be okay. Great.
>> Then I won't do that. Uh I just saved
myself a call to my assistant. So uh
>> thank you guys for having me. I'm sorry
I was such a a you know
incredibly fast hour.
>> Huge huge huge fan.
>> Best such a massive fan. You're such a
you're a you're a literally you're a
mega talent. Yeah, mega.
>> Yeah, true. Truly,
>> you guys.
>> Emma,
>> Emma, thank you guys so much.
>> Thank you for having me.
>> All the best. Feel the Hey, hey, Emma,
one thing. I want you to remember one
thing.
>> Yeah.
>> And I I hope you've lived by this credo.
>> You can always say this to every any
guy. If you want to be my lover, first
you got to get with my friends.
>> Will,
>> if you want to be my lover, you got to
get with my friends.
>> Thank you. Thank you.
>> Thank Spice Girls lyrics.
>> Take that with me.
>> Okay, got it. You're welcome. You not
knowing that that was a Spice Girls
lyric. It's one of the more painful
things.
>> Well, imagine what I thought cuz I
didn't know it was a lyric. I just
thought he was just saying that stupid
crazy sentence. Like what?
>> I was trying to connect.
>> Did you just call the Spice Girls stupid
and crazy for their
>> Were it not a lyric? If it was just this
goodbye sentence for a podcast
interview,
>> this is where I log off. What about when
James Cameron When James Cameron Cameron
won the Academy Award for best director
of Titanic? I had not seen the movie,
but when he walks up on stage, he says,
"I'm king of the world."
>> Did you say you've never seen Titanic?
>> At the time, I had not seen it. When I
saw him go up on stage and say, "I'm
king of the world." I thought, "Oh, no.
What did he just say?"
>> I've never seen it. I know.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh my god. Because you got a lot of
homework to do. Jason's listening to
Wannabe by the Spice Girls. Will, you're
watching Titanic. And Sean, just get get
Ricky You know,
>> fix your cat.
>> Get him a little fix.
>> Fix your cat.
>> Emma, thank you for being by Thank Good.
>> Sean, you were right. Great.
>> She She did it while she was sick. So
nice for her to
>> sick. Sick as a dog.
>> This is worth, you know, when we do
these late night records, it's it's, you
know, that the the stakes are high that
it that that it be a good guest and you
name it.
>> Well, let By the way, for the record, it
was a 400 p.m. record. So when you say
late night for most people they have a
different Okay. But the other thing is I
will say this and this is a compliment
to you JB. Not even a [ __ ] I'm not
there's no punch line.
>> She has a great work ethic like a lot of
people I know who started young in who
were young in uh as actors, director,
whatever.
>> She has that same thing. And you have
that same thing.
>> Uh which is she's sick blah blah blah. I
in all the years I've done stuff with
you, I've never known you to call in
sick. Not [ __ ] once.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, there was uh plenty of times when
I'd clear my day when it was 3 3:00 a.m.
and I was uh still having fun.
>> Oh, yeah. Back Sorry. Except for the
Except for when you blew back in the
day.
>> Except for when you blew your colon out
when we were doing that fight scene on
Arrested Development. You did.
>> We did.
>> You fought too hard. You broke my colon.
>> I know that's true.
>> But uh but anyway, she she does have
that great thing. She's always just God,
she's so good. You always when you start
listing off the stuff that she does and
they're all so different, you're like,
"Yeah, I missed."
>> When an actor has never sucked. Yeah.
That's that's something.
>> She's in that category. She's in that
never sucked. It's I the I always say
John Goodman number one. He's the first
guy I always think of when I think never
has never sucked and she's in that
category. There few people who fall into
that category and she's one of them.
>> Yeah, she's incredible. Um I didn't get
to ask her about I want to talk more
about La La Land about how it was shot.
>> Get ready. Well,
>> next time. Next time. next time.
>> Honestly, nobody better.
>> Here it comes. Who's got it?
>> Yeah. Well, I love Birdman, too, you
know.
>> Okay, here it comes.
>> Oh, you know what I also like? Do you
ever see by birdie? I couldn't even do
it. I couldn't even do that.
>> You're fired. Bye. Bye, birdie.
>> Wait, what? Wait a second. You can't
just start saying
>> that's it's just it's it's too
>> You're too tired. See, it's too late.
It's too late to even come up with a
buy.
>> Well, I was gonna say this. I love that
she got her name that from the baby
Spice cuz she's such a fan of the Spice
>> Spice Girl.
>> That's good.
>> Super girl.
>> Bye everybody.
>> Smartless.
Smart
less.
Smart list is 100% organic and artisally
handcrafted by Bennett Barbco, Michael
Grant, Terry, and Rob Armjarf.
>> Smart less.